<resources>
    <string name="app_name">QU Tracker</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="favs">Favs</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="API">AIzaSyAb1qAIWdXfQCJte2oPiieFtqWfVZiv9PY</string>
    <string name="FillerNumbers">##</string>
    <string name="my_buildings">My Buildings</string>
    <string name="my_residence_halls">My Residence Halls</string>
    <string name="my_dining_halls">My Dining Halls</string>
    <string name="academic_buildings_title">ACADEMIC BUILDINGS</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="favs_fragment">Favs Fragment</string>
    <string name="help_fragment">Help Fragment</string>
    <string name="quinnipiac_tracker">Quinnipiac Tracker</string>
    <string name="cas_fragment">CAS Fragment</string>
    <string name="_6">6</string>
    <string name="cce_fragment">CCE Fragment</string>
    <string name="echlin_fragment">Echlin Fragment</string>
    <string name="lender_fragment">Lender Fragment</string>
    <string name="library_fragment">Library Fragment</string>
    <string name="tator_fragment">Tator Fragment</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="cas_description">The College of Arts and Sciences building is the main hub for all things Arts. It is the main building used for Game Design students, one of the most rapidly-growing majors here at Quinnipiac. It hosts many things like general classrooms, the advising commons for students in the College of Arts and Sciences, and a state-of-the-art computer lab in the basement, which is the main room for all Game Design classes. This lab has multiple computers which can run high-quality programs like Unity, Z-Brush, Adobe Photoshop, and more.</string>
    <string name="cce_description">The Communications, Computing and Engineering building, otherwise known as CCE, is the hub for all Computer Science, Engineering, and Communications students. It holds the main Auditorium room, CCE101, which is used for a variety of different events, like seminars, celebrations, and training for RA’s. This building has 3 levels. The main level is used for film and media students, which is home to the communications students. The bottom floor has a host of the reservable study rooms, engineering classrooms, and computer labs. The top floor has standard-style classrooms used for all students.</string>
    <string name="cce_fun_fact">Fun Fact: CCE was originally planned to be a library for Law Students, but was eventually renovated to be made with classrooms for all students.</string>
    <string name="echlin_description">This building is the main building used for visitors who are interested in coming to Quinnipiac, as well as the main office for the Undergraduate Admissions and financial aid. This building is also home to many classes, especially for Nursing students, as well as other general classes.</string>
    <string name="lender_description">The Lender School of Business is the go-to building for all Business, Finance, and Economics majors. It is home to many collaborative classrooms, reservable study rooms, and the Financial Technology Center. This room has multiple Bloomberg Terminals, a student-led portfolio, and multiple connecting study rooms, with multiple stock market tickers.</string>
    <string name="tator_description">This building, connected to the Carl Hansen Student Center, which serves as a hub for all types of classes with many labs, general classrooms, and offices for faculty members.</string>
    <string name="library_description">The Arnold Bernhard Library is Quinnipiac’s most iconic building on campus. Its infamous clock tower skies over the whole quad, and is the main centerpiece for graduations. This two-story building has multiple open spaces for studying for all students. It also has multiple reservable study rooms for more collaborative, or more silent, work. It is also home to the Registrar, Bursar, Learning Commons, Student Administrative Services, Information Services, and the Technology Center. It is mainly open from 8am-12am, but during midterms and finals week, the library stays open as late as 2am.</string>
</resources>